

SUMMARY

With 8 years of experience in community management, I led brand strategies, created and scheduled content calendars for social media, drove organic audience growth and executed advertising campaigns. I am also studying Data Science to expand my skills and knowledge in data analytics.



Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina



+54 9 3413138290



lorenaaraya@gmail.com

SKILLS

Canva Design

Video Editing

Copywriting

ADS

CRM (Hubspot)

English

EXPERIENCE

Personal secretary and community manager

R.evolve.r Tattoo Studio 2021-2024

 Community manager actions. Creation and programming of the content calendar, based on the previous development of the brand strategy. Elaboration of the audience process for organic growth and execution of advertising campaigns.

Founder

The Groove Clothing 2016-2020

- Creation and programming of the content calendar, based on the previous development of the brand strategy.
 Elaboration of the audience process for organic growth and execution of advertising campaigns.
- Customer service, posnet, sales, opening and closing the till.

EDUCATION

Soy Henry

• Data Science - en curso

Linkedin Learning

- Project Manager
- Copywriting
- Facebook ads



RESUMEN

Con 8 años de experiencia en community management, lideré estrategias de marca, creé y programé calendarios de contenido para RRSS, impulsé el crecimiento orgánico de la audiencia y ejecuté campañas publicitarias. Además, estoy estudiando Data Science para expandir mis habilidades y conocimientos en análisis de datos.



Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina



+54 9 3413138290



lorenaaraya@gmail.com

HABILIDADES

Canva Design

Video Editing

Copywriting

ADS

CRM (Hubspot)

Ingles

EXPERIENCIA

Secretaria y community manager

R.evolve.r Tattoo Studio 2021-2024

 Acciones de community manager. Creación y programación del calendario de contenidos, en base a la elaboración previa de la estrategia de marca. Elaboración de proceso de audiencia para crecimiento orgánico y ejecución de campañas publicitarias.

Fundadora

The Groove Clothing 2016-2020

- Creación y programación del calendario de contenidos, en base a la elaboración previa de la estrategia de marca. Elaboración de proceso de audiencia para crecimiento orgánico y ejecución de campañas publicitarias.
- Atención al cliente, posnet, venta, apertura y cierre de caja.

EDUCACIÓN

Soy Henry

• Data Science - en curso

Linkedin Learning

- Project Manager
- Copywriting
- Facebook ads